<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JR&#39;s Research</title>
    <link>https://jakryd.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JR&#39;s Research</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jakryd.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jakryd.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakryd.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Dr. Jakub Rydzewski
Institute of Physics, Nicolaus Copernicus University (NCU)
Grudziadzka 5, 87-100 Toruń, Poland
email: jr@fizyka.umk.pl
pgp: 0x9C1099DF
phone: +48 56 611 3346
office: 573
Scientific Career
Since 2019 Assistant Professor at the Institute of Physics NCU (Toruń, Poland). 2019 Visiting Professor at the Department of Physics, University of Tsukuba, Japan, the group of Prof. Yasuteru Shigeta. 2018-2019 Assistant at the Institute of Physics NCU (Toruń, Poland). 2016-2017 Researcher at the Department of Theoretical and Computational Biophysics, Max Planck Institute for Biophysical Chemistry, Germany, the group of Prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jakryd.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakryd.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications orcid: 0000-0003-4325-4177
arXiv: 0000-0003-4325-4177
scholar: dEMXOpcAAAAJ
J. Rydzewski, K. Walczewska-Szewc, S. Czach, W. Nowak, K. Kuczera
Enhancing the Inhomogeneous Photodynamics of Canonical Bacteriophytochrome
J. Phys. Chem. B 126, 2647 (2022)
DOI:10.1021/acs.jpcb.2c00131 / ChemRxiv:n8hlc / plumID:22.015
K. Walczewska-Szewc, J. Rydzewski, and A. Lewkowicz
Inhibition-Mediated Changes in Prolyl Oligopeptidase Dynamics Possibly Related to α-Synuclein Aggregation
Phys. Chem. Chem. Phys. 24, 4366 (2022)
DOI:10.1039/D1CP05238A
J. Rydzewski, and O. Valsson
Multiscale Reweighted Stochastic Embedding: Deep Learning of Collective Variables for Enhanced Sampling</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jakryd.github.io/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jakryd.github.io/software/</guid>
      <description>Contributions github: @jakryd
PLUMED &amp;ndash; an open-source, community-developed library that provides methods for enhanced sampling, free energy estimation, and analysis of molecular dynamics (MD) simulations. Modules for PLUMED2:
lowlearner maze lowlearner maze maze (version 1.0) [1,2]
Github
maze is a code that implements enhanced sampling methods for sampling the reaction pathways of ligand unbinding. It is made as a module for PLUMED2, an engine for free energy calculations of atomistic systems and enhanced sampling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
